This is Draft season presented by
Moody's a proud partner of the New York
Football Giants. I am John Schmelk
joined by Tony Pauline. We'll have
Connor Rogers joining us in just a
little bit from SNY and NBC Sports to
talk a little bit about the biggest
questions in the 2025 NFL Draft. I'm
coming to you from the Hackensack
Meridian Hill podcast studio. Keep it
getting better. Tony, this is pro day
season. I think
Tennessee was today and I think after
today the only big one left that I think
is Indiana, right? That's it. I mean,
thank
pro day season is over. Thank you, Lord,
because if you've been following me at
Senseless Sports, I've had two sometimes
three stories a day
on pro days that started a week after
the combine.
You're correct. Today's Tennessee.
Thursday's Indiana. But more
importantly, John, and I know you've
been on this, today is the 50th
anniversary of the release of Led
Zeppelin's incredible album Presence.
Oh, yeah. I mean, I I mean, I'll be
honest with you. Like I woke my I woke
my wife up early this morning and then
we had like a party. We had we had
pancakes with like candles in them. It
was great.
To Achilles Last Stand, right? But no, I
mean, yes, the pro days are basically
pretty much done except for, you know,
the big one Indiana, which is they tied
it in I'm sorry, that's the first round
they get tied in with the spring game.
And then it's just, you know, see what
happens the final draft meetings and
then then the news will start to leak
out. Couple of individual workouts. I
know Avonte Maddox, Terrell's supposed
to work out individually. Dom Orange,
favorite of yours from Iowa State. He's
working out next week. Some of these
guys that were unable to work out
because of injuries will have their
individual workouts the first week of
April. Yeah, I thought didn't Schefter
report, Tony, and I'm going to double
check this before I say it for sure, but
I believe Avonte Maddox, Terrell might
have re-aggravated that hamstring. So
I'm not sure he's actually going to end
up doing that.
I'm going to see if I can find that real
quick. But first let's
>> be I may be incorrect because let me
just if you want to hang on, I can pull
it up. Yeah, on March 30th, Schefter
reported Clemson quarterback Avonte
Maddox, Terrell
aggravated his hamstring injury today on
the first run of his private pro day at
Clemson on March 30th. That would have
been on Monday. So Yesterday. That would
have been yesterday and I I'm incorrect
because I'm looking at the sheet right
now and it was supposed to be
the 30th. Yes. So I'm working out March
30th, 2026. So
I guess we're not going to get an
official time on Avonte Maddox, Terrell,
but you think that'll scare teams away?
I
I think with
what's going on with Jamain McCoey, not
that I thought that Terrell ever had a
chance going out with Jamain McCoey. I
don't think it's going to scare teams
away, but I think he's at best right now
the number three cornerback. I agree. So
at Tennessee's pro day today, let's
start there. According to Adam Schefter,
Jamain McCoey, remember these are
generally, especially the 40 times not
official. So you'll get hand times from
scouts that you know and that's what
these are reported, Tony. I'm sure we'll
get them
and he'll report on them when he does
get them from his sources. But Schefter
from ESPN reporting Jamain McCoey,
he remember he did not play last year
with that torn ACL that he suffered in
January of 2025, ran a 4.38 40, a 38-in
vertical jump and a 10.7 broad. And
Tony, I'll just say that'll play. And if
there was any doubt that he was going to
be the third cornerback off the board
and I think his floor is probably pick
number 10 to Dallas, right? I think
that's what we talked about or pick
number 12 to Dallas, pardon me. That's
what we talked about in our last mock
draft. We could see him going as early
as that given how well he checked out
today. Well, I I think the second
cornerback taken off the board.
>> I'm sorry, second. What did I say?
Third? I meant second. I'm sorry. So
yes, and especially with the way DeLaine
ran last week at 4.38 putting putting
those concerns about his speed to the
side. And listen, it was 4.38. Wasn't it
also like a 38-in vert and a 10.9 broad?
So you know, you know the knees healthy.
You know the knees healthy, which is
good. You know, he's going to be ready
for mini camps, OTAs, all those other
good things,
which is major
for him.
Yeah, absolutely. And look, I don't
think it would surprise either one of us
if he ends up being the best cornerback
from this class, right? Because he's got
probably the best tape along with
DeLaine and then he's a little bit
longer than than DeLaine is. So it's
just something to kind of keep in mind.
What else happened at Tennessee today
that you heard about, Tony, and then we
can start rolling down the rest of these
guys. Well, it out. Josh Josephs, 243
lbs, 38 and 1/2 in vert. Forgot 243 is
pretty good. Nine 10.9 broad. Chris
Braswell, still under 200 lbs at 199
lbs, which is the same weight he checked
in at at the combine. Long, tall
receiver.
I still like him a lot. I think he's got
great upside.
Okay. Now let's hit to a couple other
guys. Miami, Tony.
For some reason Reuben Bain did not have
his arms re-measured, which I I do not
understand given everyone's arms have
magically grown at least a half of inch
since the combine. Keep in mind that
hasn't actually happened. It's just that
whoever's measuring arms at the combine
is just not
is measuring it a little bit differently
than everyone else because it's shorter
than all the all the all-star games as
well. So no testing or new measurements
for Reuben Bain.
He'll stand on his 30 and 7/8
measurement at the combine. And then no
testing for Akeem Mesidor either. So two
guys, Tony, that win
not with crazy athleticism and bend as
pass rushers don't give NFL scouts any
testing. So they'll just have to stand
on their tape, which by the way is
excellent. I think there's a chance both
guys Bain could be a top 10 pick.
Mesidor could be a first round pick.
They'll stand on their tape. And you
know, Bain doesn't have his arms
re-measured. Cassius Howell, who had
those, you know, crazy short arms at the
combine, did have his arms re-measured
at pro day. He went from 34 30 and a
quarter-in arms to 31-in arms. So that's
that's an increase. And what it is is
the starting point. That's why it's the
starting point where they are where
they're putting the tape. But to me that
was I guess Reuben Bain's like, you know
what? The heck with this. I don't care
my my arms if they're a half-in longer,
it's not going to matter to me one one
iota. I am I don't want to say I'm
surprised. We'll talk about this a
little later on, but Mesidor not
running, I mean, he's a guy who was
considered or projected to be a 4.8 40
guy
by scouts coming into the season. So I
guess he doesn't want to be potentially
doesn't want to be exposed. So he's
like, listen, I'm going to go with my
tape, which was outstanding
coming in 2025 and I'll just roll the
dice there. Absolutely right. Okay.
Let's go The other guy that did test at
Miami's pro day, Kam Curl, Scott, who
who is again a really fun player to
watch. He's kind of one of these hybrid
corner safety types. There's a bunch of
them that are going to go in the middle,
you know, rounds two through four in
this draft. And man, he Tony, his
testing was phenomenal. Yeah. 4.33 to
4.4 flat in the 40.
Very explosive, very fast.
And why that's important is not just
that 4.33 is fast. Scouts had him as a
4.55 guy coming into the season. So
that's almost two tenths faster than
what was projected. I've talked to
people they're looking at him as a
nickel zone type of cornerback. He's
he's quick in the head as well as quick
in the feet and he's a playmaker. Don't
know about a man coverage sort of
situation for him. Better facing the
action. But again, you know, unlike say
Mesidor,
Scott got out there and ran and ran
better than expected. Yeah, and just
dynamite around the line of scrimmage.
Kendre Folk, Tony, we got some new
numbers on him.
6 ft 5, 274,
4.67 in the 40 with a 1.68 10 split.
Which really shouldn't surprise you
because he plays to that speed. He shows
that athleticism. It's just he hasn't
put it together on a consistent basis
and the 2025 film was not good, but
you're still getting 6 5 274.
Excuse me. With a 4.67, you know, he can
easily add 15 to 20 lbs. You know he's
got the underlying athleticism. I don't
think it's going to change his draft
stock all that much, but it kind of
gives
a little bit of a foundation as to why
so many of us were high on him coming
into the season. Yeah, I would have
liked to see that 10-yard split maybe a
little bit faster than that 1.68, but at
that size 274, I get it. Your guy
Emmanuel Pregnon, Tony,
32 reps on the bench, 4.84 short
shuttle, 7.733 cone. Are you happy with
that? Yeah, I mean, for a big guy,
especially that three cone, that change
of direction, I think what it tells
teams is he's he's maybe more than just
a power gap guy. We may be able to use
him in a zone system. Primarily a power
gap blocker, but if you want to pull him
across the line of scrimmage, get out to
the second level, use him in motion on
occasion, he's capable of doing that.
Again,
the tape shows that, but still for a guy
that big to be moving that fast
laterally and that quick change of
direction to 7.73, I thought it was very
good. Zion Young did not test at the
combine. He did test at his pro day,
Tony, and he did all right. Yeah. 4.75
in the 40, 10-yard split of 1.72, 31-in
vertical jump at 267 lbs. And you know,
like Kendre Folk, he's a long, linear
type of defender who will just add
weight and bulk as he physically
matures. A lot of people think that Zion
Young has definitely, if he hasn't
cemented himself into the late part of
round one, he's absolutely in that
conversation right now. No question
about it. All right. Couple of defensive
backs, Tony. Malik Muhammad, who was
great at the combine, did run a 6.95
three cone to add to that, which is very
good. Anything on their, you know, sub-7
seconds works. And then Michael Taft, a
6.83 cone, 4.15 in the short shuttle.
The safety who was at the Senior Bowl.
And that's important for Taft because
when you watch him on film, he looks
more like a downhill sort of safety. He
looks more like a straight line guy
between the numbers.
You got to think it's more of the system
because I spoke with Muhammad and we
talked about the fact that people think
he's stiff in the hips. I said, "Well,
you primarily played back off the line
of scrimmage, so wouldn't that be tough
to tell?" He says, "Absolutely." And the
same thing with Tab. It's probably a
system sort of
a scheme sort of thing where he was just
asked to play downhill. But those times,
680 and the three-cone and 415 and the
short shuttle tells you he's got that
lateral quick quickness. I still don't
know he's a true center fielder, but if
you want to put him in his own system,
there's no there should be no problem
with him getting out to the sidelines to
help out the cornerbacks in pass
coverage.
>> All right, Tony. I'll let you rapid-fire
through these. A couple day-three guys
that that tested Demonte Trayanum, the
the running back Aaron Hall,
Seydou Traore, and Corey Rucker and
Landon Robinson. Roll through those guys
as as they tested at their pro days. And
most of those guys you and I saw at the
Shrine Bowl. I mean, Demonte Trayanum
was a tribal 224 lbs, ran a 4.50 in in
the 40, 4.18 in the short shuttle, 37-in
vertical jump, also completed 27 reps on
the bench. He's always been known as a
big explosive ball carrier. Went from
Arizona State to Ohio State to Kentucky,
found his footing at Toledo this year.
But still, 224 and he runs a 4.50 and he
hits 37 in in the vertical jump, shows
you his explosion. Aaron Hall, who we
saw at the Shrine Bowl, the defensive
tackle from Duke, who really was the
star of the show on the defensive line.
297 lbs, ran a 4.92 in the 40, 7.2 in
the three-cone, 4.28 in the short
shuttle, also hit 32 in in the vertical
jump. Aaron Hall of Duke was not on the
scouting radar coming into the season,
but with his play in 2025, the way he
dominated the Shrine Bowl, and now the
testing numbers to back it up, he's
absolutely cemented himself as a
late-round pick.
Say say the Seydou Traore, the tight end
from Mississippi, again another Shrine
Bowl participant who
defenders could not cover him. It was
also a combine snub. 244 lbs at pro day,
which was 11 more than his weight at the
at the Shrine Bowl. 4.57 seconds in the
40, 40 in in the vertical jump, 10.7 in
the broad jump. I mean, here's a kid
from England. He's part of the NFL's
international player program.
Just starting to play football. 245 that
244 lbs that athleticism we saw the
football skill at the Shrine Bowl. A
non-combine guy who, like Aaron Hall, is
going to be a
day-three pick.
Corey Rucker,
incredibly productive receiver from
Arkansas State last year. 75 catches,
1,032 yards, 14 TDs after 69 catches the
year before. He came in being branded as
a possession receiver, a slow possession
receiver. Well, he ran 4.38 at his pro
day with a 1.59
a 10-yard split and a 37-in vertical
jump. So now you know he's more than a
bigger possession receiver. He has the
ability to get downfield. He did it in
the bowl game when Arkansas State played
the bowl game in Frisco, Texas, where
the Shrine Bowl practices were held.
And he he shows that speed, so you know
he's more than just a, you know, short
and intermediate pass catcher,
possession wideout. And Landon Robinson,
again a guy we saw at the Shrine Bowl. 5
5-ft 11 11 in 11 and 1/4 in, 293 lbs,
30 reps on the bench, 32 and 1/2 in in
the vertical jump, 4.78
in the 40. Now, he's got size
limitations. He's a one-gap defender, a
three-technique type of guy. The
interesting thing at his pro day is they
used him to catch passes out of the
backfield, sort of simulate him as like
an H-back fullback, and he did a great
job. So he's athletic, he's explosive.
You watch him play last year, it was go
go go all the time. And now he shows the
ability to catch the ball out of the
backfield.
You know, interesting sort of player.
You're going to have to find a place for
him at the next level, but I think he's
definitely getting a late-round
consideration. I love the way we're
we're digging deep here, Tony. All
right, let's knock off a few more pro
days here, and then we're going to be
joined by Connor Rogers here from SNY
and NBC. Mike Washington standing on his
combine, Tony, did a really nice job,
ran a 6.91 three-cone, 4.32 short
shuttle. And then Brandon Ceaser a
little bit slower than we expected. And
then what do you think about Zayvian
Harris? We did not get much on him.
Zayvian Harris, I actually spoke with,
and he didn't work out at the combine
because of a foot injury. He didn't work
out at pro day. What Zayvian Harris told
me was that he was flagged for a foot
issue
at the combine during combine medical,
sort of a plantar He didn't say plantar
fasciitis, but that's the way he
described it. They decided to have a
surgery so he could be ready for camp.
So he did no testing at all before the
combine. And the problem with the
problem with that for Harris is he was a
streaky player the past two years.
Known, but he was expected to be a good
athlete. Now
scouts have no testing numbers on him.
Brandon Ceaser, I mean, we've talked
about him on this podcast. He probably
came in a little bit smaller than we
expected at the combine, under 6-ft
tall. Everybody talked about his
athleticism. He's a big athletic guy who
has to learn to become a cornerback. You
know,
runs a 4.46 and a 4.42 at the during his
pro day. Teams were expecting
faster times than that. Not that 4.42's
bad, but they were expecting faster
times. So now you have a guy who's, you
know, as fast as every other cornerback,
still has to improve his ball skills.
That's going to hurt him. Mike
Washington, as you mentioned, ran that
blistering 40 at the combine, 6.91 at
the with at three-cone, 4.32 short
shuttle at 225 lbs, shows that change of
direction. He's definitely going to
battle Judarian Price to be the number
two running back off the board in just a
couple of weeks.
Draft season is presented by Moody's, a
proud partner of the New York Giants.
Decode risk, unlock opportunity, learn
more at moodys.com. Now we welcome in
our guest today, Connor Rogers. Does a
great job covering the NFL and the draft
and a bunch of other stuff for NBC
Sports SNY as well. Connor, good to talk
to you, brother. How are you, man?
What's happening, guys? I'm doing well.
How are you? We are doing great. Let's
bring in here anybody that you did not
see test
either at combine or pro day. If there's
one or two guys that you could say, man,
I really wish I had numbers on this guy,
who would it be?
Yeah, there's a lot to sort through
here, especially this time of year and
some late pro days. One guy I was
rechecking this morning and I was
surprised to see, and it wasn't great
for him. I think he just did the jumps,
was Derrick Moore, the pass rusher from
Michigan. That's someone that to me,
you know, you just look at it. I didn't
think he was a great athlete on tape,
but can you show everybody you're an
average athlete? And he hasn't done that
throughout this process. He obviously
likes to try to convert speed to power
as much as he can, but you know, I
thought he was just kind of average at
as at that as well. So that's the most
recent one I've been looking at where
and a lot of guys are choosing not to
test this year. I mean, the three-cone
is becoming a borderline it's like the
dinosaurs out there. Like the
three-cone, the guys that do it know
they're good at it more often than not.
And then it feels like a majority don't
even do it anymore. So it's it takes
more time than ever I would say to
navigate these waters with how many guys
wait till pro day and then what they're
told to do and what not to do.
Yeah, it's tough, absolutely is. All
right, let's get to it. Our big topic
today, our top 10 questions that I
picked out. So I guess they're my top 10
questions in in the NFL draft. And I
cheated, some of these are multi-part,
so I will warn people ahead of time on
that. So I'm going to be kind of like
the the the narrator here. I'm not going
to give much opinion. We'll go one by
one. Connor, we'll start with you.
Question number one, should Arvell Reese
be an edge player or an off-ball
linebacker? Long-term edge player,
obviously there's a little bit more
premium with that, and you see the hand
usage. That's what sticks out, the hand
usage against tackles. Now, a lot of
people forget, and I don't I don't like
this comparison, but when you're looking
at the developmental side of it, Micah
Parsons as a rookie did play off the
ball as well. It wasn't like Micah
Parsons was asked to just unleash after
the at the quarterback as soon as he got
into the NFL. So I think there's a
ramp-up period with Reese, who's still
just 20 years old, to play off ball and
on the edge as a rookie, but over time
grow into an edge pass rusher. Tony?
No, I think he I think he's both, but I
think he's an off-ball linebacker to
start off with and that you're going to
blitz on occasion. As he learns to
develop more pass rush moves, maybe
he'll become, you know, an edge rusher.
But I just think he's too fantastic as a
three-down linebacker in space, against
the run, in coverage, that you if you
try and pigeonhole him as an edge
rusher, you're taking away probably the
best part of his game. Yeah, you see I
think you start him off ball a little
bit early, and then you work him in as a
blitzer. I'm with you.
>> did. Yeah. Yeah, exactly right. And then
remember, the only reason the Cowboys
had to move Micah Parsons to edge
because Demarcus Lawrence got hurt, and
they basically ran out of guys at that
spot, and they had to move him. You're
absolutely right. All right, question
number two. This is going to be mostly
big questions towards the top of the
draft. By the way, you should check out
Connor Rogers, too, on the NFL Stock
Exchange podcast with Trevor Sikkema.
They're diving really deep now, so we're
kind of resetting at the top a little
bit for everybody.
Right now, Connor,
who's the best football player today in
this year's draft class? Jeremiah Love.
I mean, three-down player, home run
hitter, anything you want to do, any
scheme you want to run, pound-for-pound
strength, speed. I mean, what boxes he
check? The Notre Dame guys, both him and
Price, were asked to pass protect, which
is really great to kind of get that
confidence on film. I think they were
taught pretty well, too. A lot of guys
it's just effort, but with them you
could actually see the technique.
Jeremiah Love today is the best football
player in this class and can have the
biggest impact as a rookie. He is my
highest-graded player as well. Tony, how
about you?
Yeah, I'm going to disagree. I'm going
to go back to Arvell Reese. He's always
he's been my number one player on my
board probably for the past two months.
I don't that's not going to change. We
we saw the film. If you're at the
combine workouts, you know, he did some
pass rush drills. You're looking at a
guy that I think is going to start
immediately as a rookie. He's going to
be a three-down linebacker and he's just
going to get better and better the more
times you ask him to blitz the passer.
All right. So, here's the second
question. I decided to phrase it this
way because it gets specific. Which
player in this draft class will get the
biggest contract extension in four
years? I'm talking total dollars here.
Or you can even do average dollars per
year. Connor, who do you think will get
that biggest extension? Am I cheating if
I say Fernando Mendoza? I mean
>> Yes, cool. Quarterbacks don't count. Not
for the
>> Okay, you got to preface that.
>> my bad. You're right. You're right. So,
with this question is Fernando Mendoza
cuz if I didn't say that, people would
be like, "What is this guy nuts? He's
not going with Fernando Mendoza?" That's
a really, really good question because
the best players in this class do not
play the record-setting positions,
whether it's safety, running back.
Styles, I think, is truly an
off-the-ball player.
You know, there's a little risk here,
but I think I'll go with David Bailey.
If David Bailey turns into the
double-digit sack player that people
Look at that market right now. We're in
the 40s. People have like not realized
we are gone from the 30s. We have now
entered the 40s. Now, David Bailey would
have to be pretty special, obviously, to
break that market again. But even if he
he doesn't need to be a superstar, he
could just be a good pass rusher
hovering around 8 to 10 sacks early on
and he'll get a ton of money because
look at what Adetomiwa Adebawore just
got from the Commanders. He is my
highest-ranked pass rusher as well. So,
I agree with you. I'm with David Bailey.
Tony, how about you?
Well, I was going to say Fernando
Mendoza, then David Bailey. I'm going to
be a little bit different. I'm going to
say Mekhi Mews Hardman because he's a
top quarterback. Quarterbacks are paid
big-time money. You know, as we saw last
week, ran the 4.38 at the LSU pro day,
which
put aside what I thought were ridiculous
concerns about the lack of speed because
if you watch him back to his days at
Virginia Tech, he had no problem staying
downfield
with opponents. As we've talked about,
John, can play man, can play backed off
the line of scrimmage, can play in zone.
Just a versatile guy with a high upside.
Doesn't hit that 6-foot even
measurement, which a lot of people like,
but you know, listen, quarterbacks get
paid big-time money.
I I could understand why why you'd say
David Bailey. I would agree with that.
But I'm going to say Mekhi Mews Hardman
just to be a little bit different.
>> I think the other guy, too, Ruben Bain.
I think you have to put him into this
mix, too. If he ends up being super
productive, I could see Ruben Bain being
the guy that comes out on top, as well.
All right. And this might be the same
answer you gave to to the best player,
Connor. And then if it is, that's fine.
Who is the safest, most bust-proof
player in this year's draft class? It's
not the same answer because with Jahmyr
Gibbs, you have to factor in injuries. I
mean, that's the state of the running
back position, right? So, I love the
player, but I'm going to go with Caleb
Downs in this spot. And and listen, yes,
safeties can get hurt, especially
safeties that come downhill and throw
their body around. I understand that,
but Caleb Downs, to me, he's he's simply
too smart. He he really is. The work
ethic, very, very serious personality,
the way he carries himself. He was asked
to do so many things in Ohio State's
defense. He played at Alabama and Ohio
State, right? You think of the the
amount of defensive players those
programs put into the NFL. So, yeah,
I'll go with Caleb Downs, who's my
number two player in this draft. Tony.
Yeah, well, I think the other thing with
Love is what team drafts him. Because as
we saw with the Ashton Jeanty, it's not
just the injuries, it's also offensive
line. Yo, was Ashton Jeanty a bust last
year or was just the Raiders' offensive
line just awful? I, too, went with Caleb
Downs because he is a all-purpose
safety. You can put him in center field.
He can play over the slot receiver. He's
played for an NFL coach in Matt
Patricia, where he was asked to be a
two-deep zone safety and not do a lot of
playmaking last year, and he was good at
it. In 2024, he was a terrific playmaker
at the safety position. So, again, I
know people like to downgrade him
because he's a safety, but he's a
different type of player at that
position. And I think he's going to be a
day-one starter. And again, I I think
he's a plug-and-play type of guy in a
variety of schemes. All right, I'll be a
little bit different. I'll go Sonny
Styles just because I think he checks
every box, right? Smart, mature, great
in terms of meeting with NFL teams. Then
you look at his athletic testing, the
tape, the size, the length, two you
know, 6'4", 240. I just don't see a hole
in the game. Linebacker I can be a
little tough position to transition
sometimes from college to the pros,
which is why Downs is probably the
better answer. But I'll go with Styles
just because he has a better physical
profile than Caleb Downs. All right,
second part of this question. Who's the
guy, Connor, whose bust potential scares
you the most? I would say Caiden Proctor
out of Alabama, depending how high he
goes. These jumbo-sized offensive
tackles tend to go earlier than we
project at times. I mean, you think of
just from this program over the years.
And the question is cuz a lot of people
like to default back to well, if it
doesn't work at tackle and there's been
some holes there while playing tackle,
whether it's the foot speed at times,
his hands get a little wide, he loses
his balance. I felt like his playing
weight was a little top-heavy. I think
he got that weight down to a really,
really good number and he looked good at
the NFL combine. Um but you know, you
can't just assume a guy could bump into
guard if he fails at tackle. I mean, the
Giants just experienced that with Evan
Neal, right? So, from the same program
and not to school comparison, that's
dangerous to helmet scalp, but Proctor
is a top-20 pick, there's some there's
some flags there.
Tony.
I'm going to go with Ruben Bain. I agree
with Proctor being too heavy. I think
he's got to get that weight down in the
330s. It's it's much easier to play at
355 on Saturday than it is on Sunday.
I'm going to go with Ruben Bain.
Six I mean, I know everybody loves him
and I like Ruben Bain, but when you talk
about bust factor, 6'2 and 1/2, 263 lb.
We don't know what he tested. Production
just wasn't there. I mean, let's be
honest, the production was not there. Is
he a 4-3 defensive end? Is he Can he
play in a 3-4? I like his game, but I
think he's got to be coached up and I
think if he's not in the right system,
you're looking at potential
bust with Ruben Bain.
All right, I've gone back and forth
here. I think Caleb Banks is an easy one
just because of, you know,
huge men with with with foot problems,
right? I think that's I think that's
that's an easy one. That's a little bit
boring. I'm going to go Peter Woods out
of Clemson just because Yeah. Man, his
tape this year was just not great, man.
You know, Calijah Foote I have questions
about his explosion and stuff like that
and how he gets off the line, his pass
rush future. But at least I know he's
going to be a big, long, good run
defender, right? Woods this year just
seemed uninterested sometimes and
there's just such a dearth of plays
of behind the line of scrimmage. There's
not a lot of impact plays. So, I just
worry about what his film looked like
this year and what that could mean
moving forward for him in the National
Football League. All right. And by the
way, the fact I just mentioned two
defensive tackles in a rough defensive
tackle class should tell you all you
need to know about that group of players
in this year's draft. All right, next
question. How early should teams start
thinking about Jahmyr Gibbs? Connor, I
imagine that's pretty early for you.
Yeah, Tennessee at four. I have no
problem with it, right? Getting an
identity guy to help Cam Ward and be a
superstar for your new stadium and be
the engine of the offense for Brian
Daboll, both on the ground and through
the air. Obviously, it's far from a lock
that he goes in the top four, but I
think when you talk about entertaining
the idea of taking him, Tennessee at
four, I mean, four to seven feels like
the range for him. And the teams, you
know, you look at Kansas City and New
Orleans right after that. I feel like
they paid running backs big money for a
reason. I don't think they were
expecting Jahmyr Gibbs to make it to
them. I'm with you 100%. Tony, how about
you? I'm going one pick earlier, Arizona
Cardinals. I mean, they signed Kyle
Allen
in free agency, a nice situational
rotational runner. They don't have the
big-time feature back. I mean,
you start Jacoby Brissett
at your quarterback position. They do
need a right tackle. I understand that.
But you know, a warm-weather team
playing on grass. I'm absolutely If I'm
the Cardinals and I thought this all
along, I have to consider Jahmyr Gibbs
with that third pick.
Okay, I'm going to switch this number 4B
up as we just talked about Love. Better
prospect, Sonny Styles or Caleb Downs?
I'm going to mix it up for you here,
Connor. What do you think? I'd go with
Caleb Downs. I think that, you know, I
get people love Styles and for good
reason. Another guy, they both have that
intense personality, leadership, all the
intangibles you want. I didn't think
Styles was good in the National
Championship Game. And I have not heard
anyone else say that, you know, or talk
about that, which is interesting to me.
And it's not taking away from one game.
That's not the point. It's just that I
think he's been labeled as this
perfect prospect. And the perfect
prospect often doesn't exist, but I
would roll with Caleb Downs for his
consistency on the back end. And just
Tony kind of mentioned it earlier,
there's not really a role at the safety
position that you can't play him in,
where Styles might have a mini
adjustment period
adjusting to the physical nature of the
downhill NFL, dealing with pullers and
climbers. And he'll be fine, but I could
see a longer transition period there
than Downs will go through. Tony.
Yeah, I think Styles is probably going
to be drafted first, but I would go with
Caleb Downs. You can do more with him. I
mean, as we saw in that semifinal
championship game against Texas, he's a
force against the run, which alters the
momentum of of games.
And then later on,
on that scoop and score by Jack Sawyer,
you know, he's remained disciplined in
the back of the end zone with his cover
assignments. I like Sonny Styles. I love
Caleb Downs.
All right, I'm with you guys. I think
Downs probably is graded higher than me
just in terms of the type of player he
is now, but I think Sonny Styles
probably has a little bit of higher
upside because of his physical traits as
compared to Downs, who we did not get
any testing numbers on. I don't think
he's a bad athlete, mind you. But 6'2",
205,
you know, he's not Kyle Hamilton or or
like Derwin James size. You know what I
mean? All right, so let's go
>> itself to the quarterfinal, not the
national title game. But how Ohio State
didn't make it to the natty is still a
mystery to all of us. Yeah, I [laughter]
was it's funny. I I was I was
interviewing um Bill Rabinowitz who
cover he's been covering Ohio State
forever. And I'm like, "Dude, we're
talking about four different Buckeye
players as a potential pick for the
Giants at six. Like, what are we doing
here? How did you guys lose in the
college football playoffs?" It's it's
absolutely I don't know how they give up
any points. It's crazy. All right,
question five. Never mind the impact
they're going to have on offense in the
2027 draft. Did he mention the coach Did
he mention the head coach at all?
Yeah,
he did not actually. We did not get too
deep into it.
>> [laughter and gasps]
>> Question number five. All right, which
players that are going to be first-round
picks have traits, either measurement or
testing, Connor, that scares you off a
little bit?
Well, I think Tony hinted at this with
Bane, you know, and and it's not it's
Yes, it's the arm length, but you
brought up the size and the style. Like,
he he's a leverage monster. He is a
compact player that wins with power. And
I think Bane is going to be a good NFL
player. The The question is where we're
talking about his range. Is he going to
be great? Every Nobody's, you know,
sitting there going, "I think Ruben
Bane's going to be, you know, bad." The
matter is if you're taking him anywhere
from two to to nine, you're hoping he's
great, and everybody is pretty strong at
the NFL level, right? So so that's the
one to me that you think of the length,
staying off blocks, having a little
versatility in the rush, not just
rushing with power. You know, that I get
people are sick of the conversation with
Bane, but I think it's definitely at
least at least a fair one, and you could
even look at some of the offensive line
at at the top of this draft that don't
have prototypically tackle length, and
we'll see if they can actually stick at
tackle as well.
Tony.
I'm going to go with his teammate,
Adetomiwa Adebawore. Listen, coming into
the season, I thought Adetomiwa
Adebawore was woefully underrated. Now I
think people are just overrating him.
6'3", 259 lbs, really didn't do any much
testing, didn't never ran the 40, and
the probably reason why he didn't do
much he didn't run the 40 is because
scouts project him as a 4.8 40 guy. Now,
maybe he's a little bit faster than
that. You know, I don't know, but you
know, is he hand-in-the-ground guy? Is
he athletic enough to stand over tackle?
Uh you know, I like I like Adetomiwa
Adebawore. I just think uh he's being a
bit overrated at this point in time.
Probably benefited from playing on the
other side of Ruben Bane. They got
another real good player on the inside
of that defense that we saw at the
Shrine Bowl, John David Blay, who
doesn't get the credit he he deserves. I
just think with that size, the limited
growth potential, how athletic is he?
I would not take Adetomiwa Adebawore
until the second round.
All right, I'm going to go with two guys
here. I'm going to throw Keiondre Coburn
out there again. Not as measurements,
obviously, because they're spectacular,
exactly what NFL teams want. But Tony
and I were talking about what he tested
at his pro day earlier, and and and a
1.68 10-yard split, you look at some of
the other edge players, man, that is a
it's not a good 10-yard split, and that
shows up on tape where he just has
get-off, and I don't know if he's ever
going to develop into a pass rusher.
Again, I think as a run player, he's
going to be great. He's big, he's
strong, he's young. Every he checks
every box from a personality
perspective. If you talk to people
around the league, but is he ever going
to develop as a pass rusher? If you're
picking a guy in the top 15, top 20, you
want him to be a pass rusher. So, he
gives me a little bit of pause as well.
And then Cash Harris Howell with the arm
length, right? He's a guy that has a lot
of production. He has some moves on
tape. You like his pass rush repertoire,
but he's not the heaviest player. He's
just 250 lbs. Can he put that together
with his lack of length? And his his
athletic testing was good, not great.
Can that make up for maybe some of the
lack of traits where, you know, he's
more than just a nice situational guy?
I just don't know the answer to it. I
think we'll have to wait and see. All
right, second part of this question. Who
are the guys that have traits you maybe
don't love, but you just don't give a
damn because you love the player so much
you're going to pick him anyway. Connor.
Uh AJ Halsey. I mean, it's an easy one
with Halsey because of his play style.
People look at probably more so the
10-yard than the actual 40. The 40 was
4.52, which passes a threshold at safety
that you're not really concerned about.
While the 10-yard isn't it's an
acceleration is He makes up for it with
instincts and awareness, and he's so
smart down by down. His preparation
really speaks for itself. Ball skills,
uh dense frame. He Once again, he's just
not going to be the fastest or most
physically impressive in terms of
athleticism, but he's got instincts. He
always knows where to be, and he's so
dang physical on guys going over the
middle of the field. They'll think twice
about it after they get hit by him once.
Tony.
Well, John, you're going to laugh. I'm
going with Cash Harris Howell. And it's
because of the film, and he's a good
athlete. I mean, 4 What did he run? I'm
looking at it right here. Cash Harris
Howell ran 4.59 at 253 lbs at the
combine. But you watch the film, he's
more than just an edge a wide edge
rusher. He wedges his way between guard
and tackle and make plays behind the
line of scrimmage. He gets out laterally
in pursuit. He could drop him off the
line of scrimmage. I think he's a
perfect 3-4 outside linebacker as not
only an edge rusher, but a three-down
player. Love the I just absolutely love
the film. I liked him coming into the
season, and um when I watched the film,
I was like, yeah, this guy's going to be
a steal late in round one. All right,
you guys can call this shiny if you
want, but I don't care. He did not test
because he probably wasn't going to test
well. I love watching Gabe Ikard play
out of Illinois. That guy's a freaking
monster. He rushes with violence, with
effort, with speed, with power.
I've imagined he would not have tested
well because otherwise he would have
tested. But man, that dude's a football
player. So, I don't think anyone should
have any worries about not getting no
athletic testing on Gabe Ikard because
that guy is a really good football
player. All right, Connor, question six.
Who will Will there be more wide
receivers or offensive tackles taken in
round one of this draft? So, this is a
little bit of a trick, right? Because
what guys are going to be drafted and
given a shot at tackle? Will a team take
Spencer Fano as a guard, and then that
doesn't count, right? There's a chance
of that happening, of course. And then
you look at I think Proctor will get a
shot at tackle. You'd rather see him
fit, but you don't know where they're
going to go as well. A team might just
need a guard instead. It feels like the
locks at wide receiver, you know,
Carnell Tate, Mekhi Wingo, Omar Cooper,
Jordan Tyson even with the health,
they're going in the first round.
To stick to the true phrasing of the
question, I'll take more wide receivers
because I think a lot of these guys will
kick inside over time from tackle to
guard. Yeah, Tony, I think with how the
end of the first round goes, right?
Like, does Does the Clemson tackle get
pushed up? Does I Amari Mims get pushed
up? Those Those are the questions I
think that are really going to determine
whether or not there's wide receivers or
tackles here, no?
Yeah, I don't see
I I don't see Blake Miller Blake Miller
Clemson being a first-round pick. You
know, I had it 4-4 or 5-5. I Right.
differentiate. I mean, I had I could see
four tackles being taken in the first
round, Amari Mims maybe being the fifth
tackle. I can also see
four receivers being selected in the
first round,
and possibly a fifth, whether that be
Omar Cooper, whether that be Kayshon
Boutte,
you know, depending I I For me, it was
basically an even split, either four and
four of each or five of each.
Yeah, and look, I'm going to go wide
receiver just because I think they're
better players. And I'll throw
Dontayvion Wicks into that mix. He's
another wide receiver that that I think
can go in the first round there. So,
but it would not be surprising me if
we're all feeling really good about wide
receiver at pick 25, and then three
offensive tackles go in the final six or
so picks, and then we're like, "Damn, I
guess we should have went with tackle."
All right, two sub questions here. Who's
OT number one for you? Connor.
Spencer Fano. I'd give him a shot.
Once again, I get it. Like, you got to
pick your outliers wisely. You're not
going to make a living off of this, or
else you'd be in trouble. He's just so
athletic. I like the tape.
Um I think he's one of those guys that
Once again, you watch him get out of the
gate and move, but you look how quick he
is into his pass sets. When you have
that kind of base, explosive base, you
can make up for the lack of length, and
I think he does. I'm with you. He's my
number one offensive lineman. Worst
comes to worst, he can go in, and he he
might end up being the best center in
football if you move him into center.
And with, you know, with with with his
athleticism. Tony, who's your offensive
tackle number one?
Yeah, it's it's Fano, and the reason is
a lot of teams think he can play left
tackle. Was it right tackle at Utah
because of that athleticism, because of
the those movement skills, the agility.
He can move over to left tackle, and
which is why he probably will be the
Somebody brought up the point to me, Joe
Thomas didn't have 33-in arms, either,
and he turned out pretty good. So, I
think it's going to be Fano. I think he
can go as early as six to Cleveland, who
desperately needs a left tackle. And
I'll tell you, I think depending on the
team and what you're looking for,
I don't think much separates him and
Maui Nua. Like, if you're a team that
needs a tackle/guard,
I might lean more towards Maui Nua. But
if you need someone that's more of a
tackle/center, maybe then go Fano. I
think it kind of depends. I see Maui Nua
as a potential road-grading guard. I'm
not sure if Fano has the power to play
guard right away. So, I do think there's
an interesting dichotomy there between
those two players. Who's wide receiver
four?
>> if you need a left tackle? Well, then I
would pick Fano. Absolutely right. I'm
with you. Um wide receiver four for you,
Connor. I'm assuming your Or maybe your
top three aren't what I
what I think it is. No, it's Mekhi Wingo
is my wide receiver four. My top three
is Jordan Addison, Carnell Tate, Omar
Cooper Jr. I think there's going to be a
lot of interesting discussions in this
draft. Of course, with Addison, you have
the health. Carnell Tate, you have the
questions of just how physically
impressive can he be, right? We know how
well he tracks the ball and plays above
the rim, and he's got detailed footwork.
Omar Cooper, so good after the catch.
Mekhi Wingo is a solid player. He's got
to play the slot for you, right? He's
got to play He's not very big. He's not
very fast. He is fearless over the
middle of the field. I think he's tough
after the catch. I don't think he's
dynamic after the catch. When you watch
the plays, the missed tackles he forced
in college, I'm not convinced that'll
consistently happen at the NFL level. He
will finish plays. He could be a
possession player, but he's wide
receiver four for me
behind those guys, and I know that's not
a popular take. Tony, how about you?
I'm going with Kayshon Boutte,
who I absolutely love. I mean, he can
take the top off the defense. He runs
great routes. He catches everything. And
oh, yeah, by By way, he's an impact uh
return specialist, which I think is just
just makes him more attractive. I like
Casey Conception. I spoke with Malik
Muhammad about him, and Malik Muhammad
just gushed about him, what a great
route runner he is, how outstanding he
is running after the catch, how they
focused on him in that game uh late in
the season. He was still able to make
catches. Casey Conception is my number
four receiver. He's number five for me,
Tony. Number four is Denzel Boston. Um
he's got size, and I think what stands
out to me about him, he's not great
straight-ahead speed. He's not burning
by anybody. He actually has really good
side-to-side quickness, and he can beat
people miss. He comes in and out of his
routes well for a bigger player. You
look at his three-cone number, it was
very strong. I think that is reflected
on tape. I think his numbers were
depressed because as good of a college
quarterback as quarterback is at
Washington, he missed him open on tape
so many times I lost count when I was
watching his tape over the course of the
year. So I have Denzel Boston as my wide
receiver number four. All right,
question seven. Will a second off-ball
linebacker, Connor, go in the first
round, and if so, who will it be?
So in this exercise, we're not counting
Reese as an off-ball guy cuz Reese and
Styles are going to be obvious
first-round picks.
I'm going to lean no, and I think it's
going to be close. I I think you kind of
have C.J. Allen, Jacob Rodriguez, this
group of guys hovering, but I think
we're going to have a huge cluster of
them end up going in the top 45 rather
than in the top 32. I happen to agree,
Tony. How about you?
Uh I C.J. Allen will be the second one
selected, and I think he's going to be a
late first-round pick. Keep an eye on
the Steelers. There are a lot of teams
late in that uh bottom half of round one
that uh need an off-ball linebacker.
He's exceptional. People talk about the
knee issue. He had meniscus surgery at
the end of November after hurting it in
the middle of November. Hasn't been able
to run, but he he's done some other
testing, and he's uh done a lot of
position drills. Uh I think he's a guy
who is just tapping into his ability,
and as a pure off-ball linebacker, he's
got great upside. I'll be honest with
you. I did linebackers again. I finished
them off last week. I think Jacob
Rodriguez is the second best linebacker
in this draft class, and I I don't know
if I feel comfortable in the first round
with him, but
if I'm picking, he's he's my number two
linebacker, and I think he gets picked
between
30 and 40 in this draft. All right. Next
question. Who  when
will draft Ty Simpson? Connor.
I think the two spots you look at for me
are the Jets at 33 and the Cardinals at
34, and the stare down of if Arizona
feels like they got to go back into
round one to get him. That's what I I I
don't I'm just not falling into the
combo that the Jets are taking him at
16, that the Steelers are taking him at
21. Maybe, but more likely he's sitting
there waiting and kind of needs a
Jackson Dart situation or sits and waits
like Tyler Shuck did to the first half
of the second round. So uh the Jets and
Cardinals make a lot of sense for
various reasons, but I think it's going
to be a little bit of a wait for Ty
Simpson. Tony.
I I just I mean, fundamentally, I would
agree. I would not take Ty Simpson in
the first round. But from what I'm
hearing is I I think he's going to go
first round. I think he could go to the
Jets at 16. I think he could go to the
Browns with that second selection in the
first round. Uh another team trades up
into the bottom of first round. The fact
is this, everybody keeps saying, "Well,
wait till 2027 and get your
quarterback." Well, you know what? 2026
was supposed to be the 2027 uh
quarterback class with Arch Manning and
Dante Moore and everybody else. You you
you put off
getting a quarterback, you end up
looking more foolish than not. And what
everything I've heard since the combine,
as I reported, is teams like uh Ty
Simpson, he's going to go earlier than
expected. And this is I don't think it's
going to be a Shedeur Sanders type of
situation where team after team after
team that needs a quarterback in the
first round, you know, you keep hearing
the name pop up. I think he's going to
come off the board somewhere in the
bottom half of round one. I would keep
an eye on the Cowboys at 20. They do not
have a second-round pick. They need a
lot of defensive players. I would not be
surprised if they try to trade down. To
your point, Connor, they're picking
straight in front of the Steelers at 21.
So even if the Steelers don't pick him,
a team might be afraid that they will
pick him if Mike McCarthy falls in love
with the kid. So I would keep an eye on
the Cowboys as a potential trade-down
team at pick number 20. All right. Let's
go to the next question. And this is
appropriate given he just ran his pro
day today and did rather well.
out of Tennessee. How early will he go,
Connor? I think Tony and I talked
earlier. We put his floor
or rather his ceiling at 12 to Dallas.
Yeah. Yeah, that would make sense. I
mean, I would even argue maybe a Miami
at 11, but I think those days are gone.
It's great to see the big pro day
numbers. Seems like sub-44 speed,
big-time jumps, you know, paired with
phenomenal tape from 2024. I mean, just
tremendous. So it's good to see him
working out again.
I mean, I yeah, I would go from Miami at
11, which seems really really early,
probably down to the Niners at 27
because he's too good. I I mean, he's
simply just too good to fall that far,
but we've seen teams wait on injured
players, as we saw with Jahad Campbell.
We see it every year. You don't need to
go through the history of it. Don't be
shocked when a guy of this talent has to
wait till the back half of round one.
Tony. The only thing I'll say to that
is, you know, the injury was more than a
year ago. So it's not like a recent
injury. Shav- Shavon Worell.
Uh you know, I I think a lot depends on
what does Kansas City do at nine? Does
Kansas City take Mansour Delane at
number nine, you know, to basically cuz
their their their secondary has been
destroyed in the off-season via guys
that they've traded, and guys that they
lost. If Kansas City goes Mansour Delane
at number nine, I could see Miami taking
him at 11. I could absolutely see the
Cowboys taking him at 12. I don't think
he gets past Minnesota. Is there a
chance McCoy goes before Delane, guys,
or do you think that's a bridge too far?
>> I don't think so. Yeah, not not not
after the not
I hate to say not after the season
Delane has had, not after the three
seasons Delane has had, and he's put uh
those those concerns, which I thought
were ridiculous, about his speed to rest
last week. Now, John, if three years
McCoy's the better player, I wouldn't be
surprised at all. Wouldn't be I mean, he
was he was that good in 2024, but Delane
was so elite in man coverage this year
that you feel more comfortable taking
him, I would say. Yeah, I agree, but
that's why I asked the question cuz I
wouldn't shock me if McCoy ended up
being the best player in three years,
too. All right, question number two. Uh
second part of this one, we got two
more.
When will running back two be taken,
Connor, and who will it be?
God, I think it starts maybe not super
likely, but starts with the last pick of
the first round with Seattle and Jaylen
Price. I think Jaylen Price can be
thought of that highly in terms of his
talent, but it's more likely that
happens in the in the top half of the
second round when you really look at,
you know, even with the Texans look to
get more explosive with that. They have
the 38th pick cuz of the Laremy Tunsil
trade. That would be a scenario for me.
So I think somewhere from 32,
maybe down to uh 38, you could see a guy
like Price go off the board. I think
he's more liked by teams than he is by
the general public so far. Tony.
Yeah, I'm going to go with Mike
Washington. I like Jaylen Price, but the
problem is is Jaylen Price had the
benefit of playing behind Jeremiah Love.
He was never really the feature runner
at Notre Dame. You look at what Mike
Washington did this year with some a
hit-and-miss quarterback play at
Arkansas. Then he has the great uh the
combine workout. We talked about him. He
had a terrific pro day. The athleticism
is there. The size is there. Probably
the top half of round two for Mike
Washington. Uh it'll be interesting to
see, but I I think all things told with
Mike Washington, who was the feature
runner at Arkansas last year, really had
a breakout campaign, and just a
phenomenal lead-up. He was outstanding
at the uh Senior Bowl, as well. So I
mean, Mike Mike Washington has checked
every box in the pre-draft process. All
right, two more quickies here. When will
tight end three be taken, and Connor,
this is maybe maybe me perhaps
mistakenly assuming Eli Stowers will be
tight end number two. If you disagree
with that, you can talk about that, as
well. He's not in my top five. He's
tight end six for me. Yeah, I think we
need to We need to have a serious combo
about guys being able to play on the
line of scrimmage at the next level and
transitioning. And and I get it. Stowers
is athletically gifted. He is fun to
watch in the pass
game. They run a ton of manufactured
plays to get the ball in his hands, as
they should. That's smart, and hopefully
an NFL team does that for him. Um but
Sam LaPorta Ooh, I love LaPorta, too. I
I I think he's great. LaPorta is very
very talented. He had the two ACLs a
while ago in a 10-month span. It's good
to see him far away from that. Both can
have played a ton on the line of
scrimmage. They affect the pass game in
the middle of the field. Although I
think both guys are not going to go
until the third or fourth round,
honestly. So it's an interesting answer
to your question. We could have a big
gap between when Sedeeq goes. I don't
have a feel for how the league values
Stowers because he's such a
scheme-specific player, but I think
there's a huge bucket of inline guys
that'll go round three to four. I agree,
Tony.
I'm going to go late round two, early
three. It's going to be either Oscar
Delp or Max Wright. I mean, Delp,
obviously, with that uh in that Georgia
offense that had four great receivers,
and he was sharing time with Lawson
Lucky, but we saw what he could do at
pro day. I mean, he ran almost two
tenths faster at pro day than scouts
expected. He has a great amount of
upside. He's got terrific uh size. Max
Wright, more of a move tight end.
Catches the ball incredibly well. Only
had limited number of targets at Ohio
State, but he never ran uh in the in the
pre-draft process. But decided not to
run at the combine by choice. Last week
at Ohio State's pro day, he said he
wasn't running because he tweaked his
ankle at the combine. That's a big red
flag. I mean, you you when you get a guy
like Max Wright, who's more of a move
tight end, you want to get some numbers
you want to get some 40-time numbers
down on paper. They weren't able to do
that. So I think it's going to be either
Oscar Delp or Max Wright as that number
three tight end, late second, early
third. Connor, now you got to run rapid
fire, five seconds. Who's your edge
four, and how early does he go?
So if you don't put in the edge group, I
have Malachi Lawrence from UCF as edge
four. I think he will go end of round
one, beginning of round two. Such a
dynamic athlete. Needs to get better
against the run. There's no denying
that, but man, when you ask him to just
fly off the ball and use his athleticism
just to disrupt, he's pretty unique in
this class.
>> So, who's your edge three if you're not
counting Reese? Zion Young from
Missouri. Yeah, that's what an NFL body
looks like in terms of power player,
speed to power. Got after the
quarterback though at a higher rate this
year cuz he developed that inside move.
He's always been phenomenal against the
run. I would look at the Bears at 25 for
the combo with Zion Young. All right,
Connor's got to hit for NBC. Connor,
good stuff, my friend. We appreciate it,
my friend. Thank you for joining us.
>> Appreciate it, guys. Talk soon. All
right, Tony, give me yours. Who's your
edge four and how early does he go? I'm
I'm assuming I'm going to put a Reese as
your edge one. I know you don't count
him as an edge. I'm assuming it's Reese,
Bain, and Bailey. Who's your next guy
and how early do you think he'll go?
It's actually Reese, Bailey, Bain. Okay.
Uh it's either going to be T.J. Parker
or Cashius Howel. I think they're going
to go to bottom third of round one.
Uh you know, both more three-four
stand-up outside linebackers that can
occasionally put their hand in the
ground.
Interesting uh
Sorry we had to let him go, but
interesting note on Malachi Lawrence. I
reported last week at The Scouting
Sports,
he stood on the sidelines in sweats and
did nothing during pro day. Wouldn't
even didn't even get on a scale, didn't
get measured, which cheesed a lot of
teams off. I spoke to several teams,
traveled to Orlando just to work him
out, position drills. Malachi Lawrence
did nothing last week
uh at pro day.
>> Now, he he tested at the combine, but
did he do position drills at the
combine?
>> He he tested incredibly well at the
combine. Yeah, but he but he he did
position drills though, right?
>> test again.
I'm pretty sure I mean, I'll have to
look back. I don't remember that. But
remember, you know, pro days, what
happens at pro days is sometimes teams
will take a player off to the side after
the whole workout's done and run him
through a bunch of individual workouts
that are relevant to the scheme that
they run. Malachi Lawrence, basically,
like I said, stood on the sidelines in
sweats, did nothing. Reminded me of
Dawand Jones. When I was at that Ohio
State pro day with C.J. Stroud, showed
up in sweats, didn't get on a scale, did
nothing. Really really
turned off a lot of teams. And remember,
this is a job interview. So, so when you
show up not ready to work, it's going to
turn a lot of teams off. Bottom line is,
I've heard a lot of Malachi Lawrence in
the first round. I think he knocked
himself out of the top 32 picks with
that with what he didn't do last week.
That's interesting. I'm trying to
looking for Malachi Lawrence. So, that
was an auto play video off of nfl.com.
Trying to see if I can find workout
highlights from from the pro day.
Um No, not from the pro day, from the
combine. He didn't do anything.
>> I'm sorry. That's what I meant, from the
combine. Um I don't think he I'm trying
to remember if I saw him doing drills at
the combine. I know he worked out,
obviously. He had all those testing
numbers, but I don't Either way, to your
point, um not the best. Tony, this was
fun. Any Do you think Did I miss any big
questions? Like are you annoyed like,
"Boy, John didn't ask me about this."
Any other big questions that like you
think we should have hit on here when
you talk about this year's draft class
that you think need to be addressed?
Well, I I I I think the big topic last
week, which I thought was pretty uh
insane, is uh do any teams really have
Ty Simpson rated higher than Fernando
Mendoza?
>> [laughter]
>> And that was
uh you know, big conversation piece like
go in the gym and they're talking about
on ESPN.
Uh I I mean, I mean, the quick answer is
no.
It's nothing more than a conversation
piece like Shedeur Sanders being a top
10 pick a year ago. But I we probably
should have thrown that in and just had
a good laugh about it. Yeah, absolutely.
Um
Yeah, I'd be surprised if he ends up
going. Now, if this was hap If this
draft was happening on like November 1st
before Ty Simpson had a terrible last
six games, maybe we'd be having a
different conversation. But um even so,
just a limited number of starts, I think
that's That's a little risky to me in
terms of trying to trying to go there.
But look, you got to tip your cap to
ESPN, man. They can take one of their
analysts saying one thing, Tony, and it
turns into a week of content for them.
So, And look, Dan Orlovsky does his
homework. I give him credit. He sees
what he sees and he gives his opinions
even if sometimes they're not popular
with people. He thought he likes
Simpson's tape better, and that's fine.
I have I have no beef with that. But the
way ESPN's able to turn that into like
two weeks of content, God bless them.
They They know what they're doing. I
mean, my my question is, and we may
never find out, does he really believe
that? Or is he saying it just for shock
value?
>> No, I mean,
I talked to Dan. I I would I would be
very surprised. Yeah, you John, you and
I have a better chance of waking up
Easter morning with a full head of hair
than Ty Simpson does of being selected
before Fernando Mendoza.
So, you tell me there's a chance.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, Tony, good stuff.
Tell everybody what you Now that your
pro day reports are starting to wind
down here on Essentially Sports, what
what can people be looking for coming
your way?
Well, we'll have a two-round mock draft
either Easter Easter weekend or the I
keep saying Easter weekend. I know
everybody doesn't celebrate Easter. Or
the couple days after Easter. And I can
tell you Malachi Lawrence will not be in
the first round of that of that mock
draft.
The big board will be updated. 420
individual scouting reports, all the SEC
reports, all the major conferences are
in, the Mountain West is in. Just a few
little
stragglers I got. So, there'll be an
update to the big board. A lot of
information there on more than 500
players. Looking for more than just a
ticket? Elevated Experiences delivers
VIP access to the world's biggest events
from the Super Bowl to NASCAR to PGA
Tour tournaments. Don't just attend,
elevate the experience at
elevatedexperiences.com.
And then Tony, our next show coming up
next week, Dave Severson will be
Severson will be joining us from Our
Lads. He's been with us before. He does
a great job. We'll be digging a little
bit deeper next week, folks. I made this
show to be kind of a lot of stuff at the
top of the draft, right? First two
rounds, a lot of first round stuff. But
next week, we're going to do
In fact, I'll ask you right now, Tony,
while we're doing the show. How do you
want to characterize this? Do you want
to do like sleepers, overrated and
underrated at each position? Is that how
you want to handle this?
Uh
if you and Dave are happy with that,
let's go with that. I'm fine with that.
That sounds good to me. So, we'll do
that. We'll record that later this week.
It's going to post early next week as we
head barreling towards the draft, Tony.
By the time this airs, it's basically
going to be three weeks to the day. This
will go up on Wednesday. It'll be three
weeks, pretty much 21 days until the
start of the draft. It comes quick. Make
sure you stay tuned to Draft Season for
continuing coverage. And of course, the
John Schmeelk Podcast as well, where I'm
doing a bunch of interviews with draft
experts now, folks. If you're into the
draft and you subscribe to the Draft
Season Podcast, go check out the John
Schmeelk Podcast as well. It's on the
Giants Podcast Network feed. I've had
some great guests. Our mutual friend
Chad Reuter joined me earlier in the
week. Chad's awesome. He does a great
job. We got to make sure we have him on
during the year next year on Draft
Season. He's fantastic. Matt Miller's
coming up later in the week. Nate Tice
is going to join me. Former general
manager Ryan Carthon joined me. He was
with me on Tuesday. So, we had a lot of
really good guests. So, go check it out
on the John Schmeelk Podcast. That's all
the time we have for Draft Season
presented by Moody's, a proud partner of
the New York Giants. Uniting the
brightest minds to turn today's risks
into tomorrow's opportunities. Learn
more at moodys.com. Coming to you from
the Giants Podcast Studio presented by
Hackensack Meridian Health. Keep getting
better. For Tony Pauline, I'm John
Schmeelk. That's Draft Season. We'll see
you next time.